你好，你们这些漂亮的人。
Hello you beautiful people.
欢迎回来。
And welcome back.
现在，在本视频中，我们将讨论find命令最强大的功能之一
Now in this video we're going to be discussing one of the most powerful features of the find command
老实说，一般说来，命令行是一种很好的方式，一旦你得到了你的大清单，你就可以
and to be honest of the command line in general a nice how you can once you've gotten your big list
如何获取这些结果并对每个结果执行另一个命令
of results from the find command how you can take those results and perform another command on each
那些人中的一员。
of those.
这是一种令人难以置信的强大能力。
This is an incredibly powerful ability.
所以我希望你会非常兴奋。
So I hope you're very very very excited.
所以您可以在这里看到我正在使用pwt命令在桌面上。
So you can see here that I'm on the desktop using the PWT command.
我们将在这里创建一个名为copy copy的目录。
And we're going to make a directory called copy copy here.
好的。
OK.
注意到我用下划线来表示空格，这是我前面提到的很好的练习
Noticing that I'm having an underscore to represent the space that's good practice as I've mentioned
来阻止命令行出错。
to you before to stop a command line messing up.
好的。
OK.
所以我们要做的是。
So what we're going to do.
好的，假设我们要在整个文件系统中搜索每个大于100KB的文件
OK let's say that we want to search the entire file system for every file that is bigger than 100 kilobytes
并且小于5兆字节。
and less than 5 megabytes.
所以我想让你做的是，你只要试着写下那个命令。
So what I want you to do is I want is you just have a go at writing that command.
那么，您将如何从最基本的目录开始查找系统上的每个文件，
So how would you starting from the very base directory find every single file on the system and that
大于100兆字节且小于5兆字节。
is greater than 100 megabytes and less than 5 megabytes.
好的。
OK.
所以现在把视频放进去，试一试，然后回来看看你做得怎么样。
So put that video now go have a go at it and then come back to see how you did.
你过得怎么样。
How did you get on.
你成功了吗。
Did you manage it.
如果你这么做了，我真为你骄傲。
If you did I'm so proud of you.
这就像是您在使用命令行时要经常使用的一种技术。
That's like a technique that you're going to use so often when you work with the command line.
如果你没有，我真的为你有这项技能而感到骄傲。
I'm really really proud that you've got that skill if you haven't.
熟能生巧，不要去练习得多的地方。
Practice makes perfect don't where you get plenty of practice.
当你稍后完成你的任务时。
As we as you go with your assignment later on.
但我就是这么做的。
But this is how I go about it.
好的。
OK.
我会从基本目录开始使用find命令。
I'd use the find command starting at the base directory.
所以我们要按Can键输入一个劈开。
So we're going to press can type a slash.
我们将使用type选项指定只需要文件。
We're going to specify that we want only files by using the type option.
我们会说大小必须大于100千字节，大小必须小于5
We're going to say the size has to be greater than 100 kilobytes and the size has to be less than 5
兆字节。
megabytes.
现在，因为我们从这里的基目录开始，以确保我们的外部命令具有
Now because we're starting at the base directory here to make sure that our foreign command has the
能够进入我们要在整个命令前加上伪前缀的每个文件夹，因为否则
ability to go into every folder we're going to prefix this entire command with a pseudo because otherwise
我们会收到权限访问错误，而我们不想要这些错误。
we get permission access errors and we don't want those.
因此，让我们以管理员身份运行整个命令。
So let's just run the whole command as the administrator.
好的。
OK.
所以如果我们运行它的话。
So if we if we run that.
好的。
OK.
我们会找到一大串结果，但我会交出我的密码。
We're going to find a big list of results but I give in my password.
我们会发现一大堆结果都出来了。
We'll find a massive list of results comes out OK.
顺便说一句，这些东西中的一个正在运行。
And by the way one of these things are running.
实际上，您可以通过按住Ctrl键并在命令行上取消它的运行
You can actually cancel it from running any come on the command line by holding the control key and
按C键确定。
pressing C OK.
我不会让命令停止运行的。
I'm not will that will stop the the command running.
好的。
OK.
如果你知道它花了太长时间，你会不会输入错误的东西，然后你意识到了，但你并没有意识到这一点
And if you know it it's taking too long will you type something wrong and you realize it and you don't
我得等事情做完了才行。
have to wait until the thing finishes.
好的，但是我们得到了一大堆结果。
OK but we're getting a whole bunch of results.
实际上我们可以告诉你有多少个。
Actually we can tell you how many there are.
当你看到通过输入单词COUNT来看的时候，你可以看到我们得到了3000和31个结果。
When you see see by piping into the word count Come on you can see we got 3000 and 31 results.
这是相当多的结果。
That's quite a lot results.
好的。
OK.
现在假设我们想要复制这些文件中的每一个3000个文件中的每一个文件
Now let's say that we want to copy every single one of those files every single one of those 3000 and
它的结果与此Copy Here文件夹的I find Command标准相匹配。
it one results that matched I find Command's criteria to this copy here folder.
好的。
OK.
我们怎么才能做到这一点。
How would we do that.
如果我使用另一个选项清除屏幕，我们可以使用另一个选项
Well the way that we would do that is using another option if I clear the screen using another option
对于名为exec选项或精确选项的find命令，它代表EXECUTE。
for the find command called the exec option or the exact option stands for execute.
我，我要这么做，我要把屏幕最大化，这样就更容易看到了。
And I am I'm going to do it I actually going maximize the screen and so it has a bit easier to see.
所以我们说，好的，一旦你在这里完成了每个结果的搜索，执行一些操作。
So we're saying OK once you've done the search here on each result execute something.
现在，您只需像往常一样在此处键入命令即可。
Now here you just type the command as you normally would.
所以我们会说Copy，因为我们将使用cpe命令进行复制，您知道，这与我们通常的做法一样
So we'd we'd say copy because we're going to use the CPE command to copy which is you know like we normally
会的。
would.
现在，如果您还记得copy命令是如何工作的，那么您要做的就是说出您想要复制的内容，然后
Now if you remember how the copy command works first what you do is you say what you want to copy and
然后你说在哪里。
then you say where.
好的。
OK.
所以你说你想复制什么，然后说在哪里。
So you say what you want to copy and then you say where.
我们知道要将其复制到桌面上的什么位置。
Well we know where we want to copy it which is going to be on a desktop.
好的。
OK.
它将在Copy Here文件夹中。
And it's going to be in the copy here folder.
这就是我们要复制的路径，这里是我们匆忙回家的时候，劈开桌面上的斜杠，劈开复制到这里。
So that's our path to the copy here for us rush home slashes the slash desktop slash copy here.
我们只要把波浪号也放在那里，就可以把另一个更短，这样就可以了。
We can rather the other shorter by just putting the tilde there as well that would be fine.
好的，但是我们要复制什么呢？
OK but what do we want to copy.
嗯，我们想要复制这些文件中的每一个。
Well we want to copy every single one of those files.
表示这一点的方法是使用一对方形弯曲括号。
The way to represent that is by using a pair of square squiggly brackets.
好的，那么你输入一些波浪形的括号。
OK so you type some squiggly brackets.
填满这个空间的是那些文件中的每一个。
And that what fills that space is every single one of those files.
好的，反过来，它会说将某个文件复制到此目录，然后将Faltu复制到此目录
Ok so in turn it will say copy whatever file one was to this directory then copy Faltu to this directory
并将4：03复制到此目录。
and copy 4:03 to this directory.
所以我们现在已经得到了全部3000个结果。
So we've got all 3000 results now.
当您构建这些表达式时，您可以拥有多个这样的表达式。
When you build out these these expressions you can have multiple of these.
您知道，如果您出于任何原因需要执行您的命令，但是一旦您像我们一样创建了它
You know if you needed to in your command for whatever reason but once you have created it like we have
所以我们说，好的，找到每个大于100千字节，小于5兆字节的文件。
so we're saying OK find every file that's greater than a hundred kilobytes and less than 5 megabytes.
找到所有这些文件后，对其执行Copy命令，并将其复制到我们的Copy Here目录
And once you find all those execute the copy command on it and copy it to our copy here directory on
我们的桌面。
our desktop.
然后，当她完成所有这些操作以结束命令时，您不能只按Enter键。
And then when she finished all of that to end the command you don't just press enter.
您必须在完成EXECUTE选项时告诉它，完成此操作的方法是按
You've got to tell it when you've finished your execute option and the way you do that is by pressing
反斜杠，然后是分号。
a backslash and then a semi-colon.
好的。
OK.
所以你看到分号里的反斜杠，那就是命令完全结束了。
So you see the backslash in the semi-colon and that is the command completely finished.
好的。
OK.
所以，如果你继续跑，那就没问题了。
So if you go ahead and run that's OK.
我们只等一会儿，直到我们的节目回来，它所做的就是复制和粘贴
And we wait just a little while until our show comes back what it is doing is it is copying and pasting
将这些选项中的每一个都复制到我们的Copy Here文件夹中。
every single one of those options into our copy here folder.
好的。
OK.
所以我想如果我现在停下来，然后把这个关闭，然后去找版权所有者，我们走吧，你会
So I guess if I stop that for now and then close this and go to the copyright holder there we go you'll
请注意，我们实际上已将这些文件中的每一个文件复制并粘贴到我们的Copy Here目录中
see that we actually have every single one of those files copied and pasted into our copy here directory
或者至少和我停止运行命令之前一样多。
or at least as many as it did before I stopped running the commands.
这很棒，但是我们已经设法只使用find命令，而不仅仅是找到我们想要的东西。
It's awesome but we've managed to just use the find command and not only find what we want.
而且还对每个结果执行命令。
On the whole system but also execute a command on each of the results.
因此，根据您正在运行的硬件类型，顺便提一下，引入以下命令
So just as an aside depending upon what type of hardware that you're running bringing this command in
这可能会给您的计算机带来一些麻烦。
it's entirety might give your computer a bit of trouble.
因此，如果您发现虚拟机崩溃，只需尝试将整个命令运行到
So if you're finding that your virtual machine crashes just try and run the whole command to just a
最大深度为4以保存它，您知道，可以找到文件中的每个文件。
maximum depth of four to save it you know finding every file on your files.
这应该会大大降低您计算机上的负载，或者尝试最大深度
This should reduce it quite significantly the load on your computer anyway or try and maximum depth
三个人中的一个。
of three.
如果您发现您的虚拟机崩溃，我不确定这是否能阻止任何问题。
I'm not sure that that should stop any problems if you find your virtual machine is crashing.
但首先我们不想做的就是看一下这个命令。
But first we don't want to do at the minute is just take a look at this command.
这不是很棒吗。
Isn't that awesome.
我的意思是，考虑到您没有，您可能对Linux命令行一无所知，只是
I mean considering that you haven't you maybe didn't know anything about the Linux command line just
几个视频之前。
a few videos ago.
现在你看到这个命令，你可能会想，哇，如果我真的走了那么远
Now you're looking at this command and you're probably thinking wow if I actually come that far and
这就是链接上线的原因，不是吗，复杂得令人难以置信。
this is the thing the links come on line isn't it at unbelievably complicated.
这只是几个概念。
It's just a few concepts.
如果他们向你解释得很糟糕，或者你不太明白他们的意思，那可能是绝对的
If they're explained to you badly or you don't quite understand what they mean it can be an absolute
噩梦。
nightmare.
但是一旦你理解了它们，就很容易把你知道的这里的几块积木
But once you understand them it's very easy to take you know just a few building blocks here and build
一种令人难以置信的强大力量。
something incredibly powerful.
现在，您找到了一种搜索100KB到5KB之间的每个文件系统的方法
So here you are you found a way to search for every filing system in between 100 kilobytes and five
MB大小，只需一个命令即可将它们全部复制到特定文件夹。
megabytes in size and copy them all to a specific folder in just a command.
但是现在你知道怎么做了，所以我认为这很令人惊讶，我真的想在这个视频中暂停一下
And yet now you know how to do that so I think that's amazing and I really wanted to pause in this video
我只想说我为你能走到这一步感到非常非常自豪。
just to say I'm very very proud of you for making it this far.
在这一节的结论第4节中，你会得到更多的祝贺
And you're going to get many more congratulations on this in the conclusion section 4 for this section
当然可以。
of the course.
现在我想要做的是，我想在这里稍微继续讨论一下这个选项。
Now what I want to do is I want to move on just a little bit to talk about this exact option here.
这个确切的选项与执行命令一样令人敬畏，但它并不是所有事情中最安全的。
This exact option is awesome as is to execute a command but it's not the safest of all things.
好的，所以如果可以的话，可以不使用确切的选项，而实际上可以输入OK选项。
OK so if you can do if is instead of using the exact option you can actually type the OK option.
好的。
OK.
这将做的是，它将做完全相同的事情。
And what this will do is it'll do exactly the same.
它的工作原理完全一样，你不需要改变任何东西。
It works exactly the same you don't have to change anything.
而不是直接做动作。
But instead of just doing the action directly.
如果我尝试这样做，它不会在每次试图复制什么东西时都会问我它是好的还是
If I if I try this it will noce ask me every time that it tries to copy something whether it's OK or
不。
not.
如果我键入y，它将继续，我键入Y，它将继续一段时间。
If I type y it will continue and I type Y it'll continue for time.
不不会的。
No it won't.
诸若此类。
And so on.
因此，我可以在这里选择它对每个文件执行的操作。
So I have a choice here about what it does for each file.
现在，如果您有数千个文件，这显然是一个巨大的痛苦，但这是一件可以承受的好事
Now this would clearly be a massive pain if you have thousands of files but it's a good thing to bear
请注意，如果您正在为几个文件执行某些操作，并且您正在执行破坏性操作，如删除
in mind if you are doing something for a few files and you're doing something destructive like deleting
或者移动文件，而不是像本例中那样只复制文件，并且您想要加倍确保
or moving files instead of just copying like in this case and you want to make sure doubly sure that
没有任何问题，您可以使用OK选项。
nothing goes wrong you can use the OK option.
然后是EXEC选项，以实现完全相同的功能。
So then the exec option in order to do exactly the same stuff.
因此，OK选项与EXECUTE选项完全相同，您无需更改其他选项
So the OK option is exactly the same as the execute option you don't have to change anything else from
从现在开始只需记住，你知道它比使用完全相同的
it from here on just just bear in mind that you know it's it's it's a bit safer than using the exact
但是你知道，如果你有成千上万的文件要做，这是一个巨大的痛苦。
option but it's you know it's a massive pain if you've got thousands of files to do.
正如我所说的，我真的真的为你在这一部分中所取得的进展感到自豪
So as I was saying I'm really really proud of you for getting as far as you have in this section in
这个视频。
this video.
顺便说一句，您可以通过按下Ctrl来取消退出OK选项，然后如您所见
And by the way you can cancel your way out of the O.K. option by pressing control and see like you see
我刚做完这里的事。
I've just done here.
当然，您可以通过按Ctrl和Al来清除屏幕。
And of course you can clear the screen by pressing control and Al.
但我想在下一个视频中做的是，我们将把这一点发挥到极致。
But what I want to do in the next video is we're going to take this to the extreme.
好的，我们将真正向您展示find命令可以通过执行一些查找来实现多么强大的功能
OK we're going to really really show you how powerful the find command can be by doing a little finding
在下一个视频中，我们将创建一个名为“大海捞针”的文件夹，这是一种类似于大海捞针的活动
the needle in the haystack kind of activity in the next video we're going to create a folder called
包含500个其他文件夹的干草堆，在每个文件夹中，我们将再创建100个文件。
haystack that contains 500 other folders and in each of those folders we're gonna make another 100 files.
这将是非常容易的。
This will be very easy.
利用我们在支架扩展方面的知识。
Using our knowledge of our knowledge of brace expansion.
但是在其中一个文件夹中，我们将随机创建一个名为针t xti的文件，然后
But inside one of those folders at random we're going to create a file called needle t XTi and then
我们将使用find命令在大海捞针，并将其移到主目录中。
we're going to use the find command to find the needle in the haystack and move it into our home directory.
好的，在大约50000个可能的文件中，我们将找到那个文件，并将其精确复制到需要的位置
OK so out of about 50000 possible files we're going to find that one and copy it exactly where we need
这将是如此容易做到，你不会相信的。
and it's going to be so easy to do you won't believe it.
好的。
OK.
我们能做的就是转到下一个视频，我们在那里见，大海捞针。
We can do is we'll shift over into next video and I'll see you there to find the needle in the haystack.